

const questions = [
    {
        question : "blow up (The car's engine blew up just before the finishing line)",
        answer : "exploser",
        QR: "blow up"
    },
    {
        question : "blow up (I needd to blow the tyres up on my bike)",
        answer : "gonfler",
        QR: "blow up"
    },
    {
        question : "break down (Our car broke down in the middle of a snow storm)",
        answer :"tomber en panne",
        QR: "break down"
    },
    {
        question : "bring up (You should bring that point up at the meeting)",
        answer :["mentionner","soulever"],
        QR: "bring up"
    },
    {
        question : "bring up (I was brought up in England)",
        answer :["élever","éduquer"],
        QR: "bring up"
    },
    {
        question : "call of (The company sports day has been called off because of the weather)",
        answer : "annuler",
        QR: "call of"
    },
    {
        question : "carry on (Don't let me interrupt you. Carry on with your explanation)",
        answer : "continuer",
        QR: "carry on"
    },
    {
        question : "carry out (They are carrying out a study ibto the causes of global warming)",
        answer : "réaliser",
        QR: "carry out"
    },
    {
        question : "catch up with (You go ahead - i'll catch up with you later)",
        answer : ["rattraper","rejoindre"],
        QR: "catch up with"
    },
    {
        question : "come across (I came across an old photo of you yesterday)",
        answer : ["tomber sur","trouver par hasard"],
        QR: "come across"
    },
    {
        question : "come up with ( He's come up with a solution to our problem)",
        answer : ["proposer","suggérer"],
        QR: "come up with"
    },
    {
        question : "cut down on (The doctor says i have to cut down on drinking and smocking )",
        answer : "réduire sa consommation",
        QR: "cut down on"
    },
    
]

export default questions